A Guide to the Kenneth E. Crouch Music Collection, 1947-1958
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Kenneth E. Crouch Music Collection 1947-1958
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
3623,-a
This collection consists of research material for songs.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift on 1950 December 20 and 1951 March 22.
Contents List
- Manuscript
  - Manuscript of "Our Singing Land" by Kenneth Crouch n.d. (Box 1)
- Research Material for Songs
  - State Songs
    - Alabama 1947-1948 (Box 1)
    - Alaska 1947-1956 (Box 1)
    - Arizona 1947-1948 (Box 1)
    - Arkansas 1947-1955 (Box 1)
    - California 1947-1955 (Box 1)
    - Colorado 1947-1949 (Box 1)
    - Connecticut 1947-1951 (Box 1)
    - Delaware 1947-1948 (Box 1)
    - Florida 1947-1948, 1953-1957 (Box 1)
    - Georgia 1947-1948, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Hawaii 1947-1955 (Box 2)
    - Idaho 1947-1955 (Box 2)
    - Illinois 1947-1948 (Box 2)
    - Indiana 1947-1948 (Box 2)
    - Iowa 1947-1948 (Box 2)
    - Kansas 1947-1948 May (Box 2)
    - Kansas 1948 June-1951 (Box 2)
    - Kentucky 1947-1951 (Box 3)
    - Louisiana 1947-1955 (Box 3)
    - Maine 1947-1948 (Box 3)
    - Maryland 1947-1948 (Box 3)
    - Massachusetts 1947-1955 (Box 3)
    - Michigan 1947-1957 (Box 3)
    - Minnesota 1947-1948 (Box 3)
    - Mississippi 1947-1955 (Box 3)
    - Missouri 1947-1955 (Box 3)
    - Montana 1947-1955 (Box 3)
    - Nebraska 1947-1951 (Box 4)
    - Nevada 1947-1949 (Box 4)
    - New Hampshire 1947-1955 (Box 4)
    - New Jersey 1947-1956 (Box 4)
    - New Mexico 1947-1949 (Box 4)
    - New York 1947-1952 (Box 4)
    - North Carolina 1947-1949 (Box 4)
    - North Dakota 1947-1949 (Box 4)
    - Ohio 1947-1954 (Box 4)
    - Oklahoma 1947-1949 (Box 4)
    - Oregon 1947-1955 (Box 4)
    - Pennsylvania 1947-1951 (Box 4)
    - Rhode Island 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - South Carolina 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - South Dakota 1947-1950 (Box 5)
    - Tennessee 1947-1955 (Box 5)
    - Texas 1947-1951 (Box 5)
    - Utah 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - Vermont 1947-1955 (Box 5)
    - Virginia 1947-1948 (Box 5)
    - Washington 1947-1957 (Box 5)
    - West Virginia 1947-1955 (Box 5)
    - Wisconsin 1947-1955 (Box 5)
    - Wyoming 1947-1958 (Box 6)
  - Former Possessions and Territories
    - Canal Zone 1947-1948 (Box 6)
    - Guam 1951-1952 (Box 6)
    - Philippines 1947-1948 (Box 6)
    - Puerto Rico 1947-1953 (Box 6)
    - Samoa, American 1951-1957 (Box 6)
    - Virgin Islands 1955 (Box 6)
  - Military
    - United States Army Song 1947-1952 (Box 6)
    - United States Army Air Force 1947-1953 (Box 6)
    - United States Cavalry 1947-1949 (Box 6)
    - United States Coast Guard 1947 (Box 6)
    - United States Marine Corps 1947-1950 (Box 6)
    - United States Maritime Service 1948-1949 (Box 6)
    - United States Navy 1947-1955 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Confederate States of America 1947-1952 (Box 7)
    - The Republic of Texas 1947-1949 (Box 7)
    - Songs of the American Colleges n.d. (Box 7)
    - United States National Anthem 1947-1949, 1957 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous 1957-1959 (Box 7)